Diversity is a total Almost
like real estate. Homes are a horrific
investment. Housing limits options. Why
would I want to lock myself in this?
Because I think these are just uh
cultural beliefs that the banking system
still does. This is a cultural thing. It
is not an investment.
>> But there are a lot of people that make
their fortune with real estate, right?
Is it still possible today?
>> I think everyone is already at peak
consumption, especially the super rich.
They can't have any more villas. They
don't need any more lexas. They they can
only have so many Bugattis and cars and
purses and mistresses and pillows and
boats and airplanes. Super wealthy, very
sophisticated players in the last year
studying this market and they're now
coming in and they're coming in with a
very different appetite. You're
absolutely out of your mind. I'm like,
"Oh my god, you guys are going to end up
broke."
[Music]
>> Stacking crypto like it's fame. If you
want success, then take a look away.
Today's guest is someone our viewer
absolutely loved last time. Um, he was
on and the feedback was off the charts.
Hello, Gary.
>> Hello. Good to see you, Bonnie.
>> I think people really resonates with
your comment um with you said owning a
home is a terrible, terrible, terrible
investment and you used three terribles.
>> I'll just cut to the chase. Owning a
home is a horrible, horrible, horrible
investment.
>> Some people hated it, some people loved
it. Um, is it really that bad?
>> Well, mathematically I think I can prove
that it's a horrific, terrible times
three investment. Um, the other thing is
I think they really take up a lot of
time
>> and energy. You know, a husband and wife
get married. uh Sally and Bob get
married and uh it's a beautiful April
day and then you know the culture of
Sally says you must in order to be
successful you must own a home. The
truth is unless you could pay cash for
that home you don't really own it. So
you really they're really saying hey you
need to take a liability out put some
weight on your back to own something or
at least pretend to the public that you
own something. Sally and Bob are all
excited. They're romantic. And then on a
Saturday afternoon, Bob's got to go fix
the roof or Bob's got to fix the
plumbing. Now, all of a sudden, Sally
really married a plumber and a roof
taker maker, right? So, you see how the
house now is starting to interfere with
a relationship because I don't think the
lady really wanted to hire a plumber or
or marry a plumber. you're literally
spending time taking care of this thing
instead of taking care of each other.
And no one ever has walked into my home
and said, "By the way, before I step
into this door, do you own or rent it?"
As if it would be a different experience
with me, whether I had a mortgage or did
not have a mortgage or had a lease. So,
I think these are just uh cultural
beliefs that the banking system sold us
so that we would own a home. Maybe in
1950 it was cool, but in 2025
when you have a transient world where
we're
can speak to people in Asia uh at the
click of a switch with high stream
video. Why would I want to lock myself
into a zip code into one county or one
province or one anything? It's limited
my options to it's limited my options.
housing limits options.
>> But there are a lot of comments people
say, um, oh, the fact that, you know,
you say owning a home is a bad
investment. It's just in the US, you
know, um, Taiwan and Asia are different.
They said,
>> well, it depends if if you're if you're
buying a home because you like to sweep
up the floors and take care of things
and have this place that you call home.
Like I own, you know, I have a mortgage
on a home. I I wished I didn't. By that
I mean this house that I live in is not
worth $120 million. Had I invested the
same amount of money in 2020, October of
2020, in the home I live in, I think
you're going to come to an event at my
house in November, you let me know if
this house is worth $120 million or not.
Had I invested that same amount of money
in October of 2020 into Bitcoin, it
would be worth $120 million today. like,
did my house really increase in value?
No. You're going to sit here and go,
"Dude, this house is nice, but it's not
worth $120 million. How many homes could
I have rented or bought? How many hotels
could I have bought for $120 million?
The return over 10 years, 3 years, or 20
years is very, very different."
>> I actually looked it up. So, because
people commented like, "Oh, it's
different in uh US and Taiwan." So I
looked it up the past 20 years. Taipei
and LA comparison price growth Taipei
2.5 to 3x LA 2 to 2.5x but net yield
Taiwan is actually lower than 0%. LA 2
to 4% growth. So it's not good.
>> I think if you run the numbers the the
numbers it's not an investment. It's a
luxury
>> and you no one said anyone had to own a
home. When you come to America, you
don't buy the whole hotel. You rent a
room and you have no shame about it.
It's efficient. This is a cultural
thing. It is not an investment. I think
it's a liability. It's something that
you It's like you're walking around with
luggage all the time. You can't easily
get out. If I offered you a job for half
a million dollars today and you lived in
a I have literally had people say,
"Listen, I can't move from Arizona
because my two-year-old kid is building
his social network."
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. And well, the real deal is the
wife likes having mom nearby so she can
have a rent a nanny. But the guy passed
on a half a million dollar job because
he owns a house in Arizona and has a
cheap interest rate. I hear this all the
time. I I can't move. I have a 4% note.
>> Really? You have a four? So, you're
worried about paying two more percentage
points on a 100 grand
because you don't want to leave Arizona.
You You want to leave Arizona, but you
want that 4% note, and you won't move it
for 6%. It's a 2% delta on a 100 grand.
It's It's nothing. $2,000 a year.
to not have optionality. I don't get it.
That's why I love Bitcoin because it
gives me unbelievable upside potential
and unlimited optionality.
>> Can I say it's also an emotional thing
because I know I'll never get kicked out
of my house.
Taiwan fashion.
Stra X coupon
radar.
I bought uh my first home seven years
ago and the price doubled, you know,
since then. But people look at it and be
like,
>> did you sell it?
>> No.
>> Did you sell it?
>> Why not? Why not?
>> You doubled in seven years. That's a
good That's a good return.
>> Yeah. Like people would look at it and
be like, "This is great." But if you uh
look at it in Bitcoin terms, it's
terrible.
horrific.
>> But at the time, you know, this like you
said, it's probably like a luxury. It's
an emotional comfort and that was the
best per purchase, right?
>> The thing is though, you haven't even
considered selling it. It's doubled in
price. If Bitcoin doubled in price, if
you'd bought Bitcoin, you'd have bought
Bitcoin
$16,000. You' have 10xed
>> to 10x it right now for seven. Seven
years is probably more than that, but
let's call it a 10x. You would have put
$100,000 into your home. You'd have made
$1.2 million right now. You would have
already looked at selling your Bitcoin
from 16 to 35. You'd have been like,
that's a double.
You would have, but with your house, you
never even think about it. Now, I'm
going to say that unless you think house
prices are going to go up 8% a year
forever, you've probably made
the most amount of money you're going to
make on that house. That means $200,000
house, that's a $16,000 a year in
increase every year. On the Bitcoin, you
would have probably sold it at 355.
And the house, you didn't even think
about it. And that return is going down
now. That return will not go up from
here. the irr, right? The internal rate
of return, time value of return.
>> Um, you know, I made all my money on
this house probably in the first two
years and everything after this is going
to be less return.
>> Well, but there are a lot of people that
make their fortune with real estate,
right? Yeah. Is it still possible today?
I
>> I mean, I've got a I've got a famous
brother that he's made a lot of money on
real estate. Is it possible? I think
it's possible the way he's doing it, but
he's buying. Let's not conflate real
estate. There's three buckets of real
estate really. There's well maybe four.
There's multi-dwelling, which is what we
do.
Apartments that generate income.
There's homes, which is what we're
talking about. Homes are horrific
investment. There's farming,
agricultural, okay, which really
requires you to farm the land. And then
there's corporate commercial. corporate
commercial is destroyed.
>> I mean, it's absolutely
in America, it's just absolutely
hammered. This is all the stuff in 2020
and 2021 that was bought and it was
bought with zero uh you know, all
interest
>> all interest 2% and then that 2% went to
six and now people are upside down. If
you really analyze the market, all that
real estate, it's the 2020 and the 2021
and the private equity stuff, all that
vintage was over, it just got
overpriced.
Uh, and it got overpriced with extremely
cheap debt that now has changed and they
can't afford the the rate. So, I think
you can make money in real estate. I
think it's uh it's to me it's real
estate was an awesome investment until
Bitcoin came around. If you're an old
family and you've been doing real estate
your whole life, you are doing yourself
an absolute disservice if you do not
understand the relationship or the
correlation between
uh a physical piece of real estate,
corporate, residential, or otherwise in
Bitcoin. You really do. If if you have
some kind of challenge and you don't
understand it, it you serve yourself
very very well to understand why that
is. Maybe I'm wrong,
>> but it's worth your time for your debate
for sure.
>> Remember Grunt said, "Can you live in
Bitcoin, right?
>> You don't have a use. You don't have a
use. You don't have
>> What would happen to Carl?"
>> Nobody's sleeping in Bitcoin, bro. Like,
like you guys got to get off this
craziness about investing.
>> Can you sleep in a Bitcoin?
>> I don't think so. Um, real estate is
still I I think his argument is real
estate is still um very big asset class
and people like us, we love Bitcoin and
all we talk about is Bitcoin, but we
cannot ignore that big asset class.
>> Well, I don't think anybody's ignoring
it. Um,
one, I think most people already have
uh all the real estate they need.
>> This this is why I'm very bearish.
uh on legacy assets as you and I know
them.
I think everyone is already at peak
consumption. Now think with that right I
think everyone especially the super rich
in fact the rich I think there they
can't have any more villas they don't
need any more Rolexes they they can only
have so many beadis and cars and purses
and mistresses and villas and boats and
airplanes there gets a point when you're
like hey I don't need another 650 okay I
don't need another Colorado house now
what don't they have so I think when
Grant I I will say one thing it's going
to be really interesting to watch his
progression now I will
predict his progression will be you will
see a man from legacy assets change to
Bitcoin so hard he will understand the
value of having premier piece of real
estate that is not locked up in a ation.
We are having floods all over this
country right now. Chicago, New Mexico,
Texas. It's not hitting Bitcoin.
>> These storms are not harming Bitcoin.
And uh you cannot tell me you're not
sitting on tons of real estate and
there's lightning storms and all kinds
of events and fires and wars and you
don't have exposure. You cannot pick up
a piece of real estate and just move it.
So there's a huge value. Oh wow. I have
a rare piece of real estate. 3500
billionaires on this planet.
3500 billionaires on planet Earth.
Each of them worth an average of four
and a half to five billion dollars. I
think 30 or 40 of them are in Bitcoin.
>> Oh, that's not a lot. That is that is uh
10% 10% is 350
billionaires
>> 5 and a half billion dollar valuation
each.
They all buy 20%.
We have major
analytics firms now suggesting 30 and
40% allocation to Bitcoin.
uh a 300 billionaires decide they're
going to buy $300 billion worth of
Bitcoin each one billion each. If it
goes to zero, which is impossible to do
at this point, their life does not
change.
If it increases 10x,
my god.
Okay. The asymmetrical
nature of this trade for extremely
wealthy people. These people are coming
in buying thousands of Bitcoin right
now. They are not buying 10 Bitcoin.
They are. And this is the this is my
point about my brother. My brother
represents a substructure or subsection
of a certain type of investor.
I am was in front of him being a little
crazier, much more risk, happy to be
early, don't care about legacy, didn't
have a business I was trying to protect.
And the people even before me that came
in 13, they were just anarchists, right?
>> And and and and some of them won lottery
tickets and some of them understood what
we were doing. But now you have a real
industry here, a two trillion dollar
industry.
Um, my brother was never going to double
his real estate position. Not not
possible. And that's how I pitched him.
Hey, if you want to double or triple
your position, you're going to have to
do something out of the box. You can't
keep going to the bank going, "Hey, can
I borrow $80 million?" And then it's
just too much work.
And and now you see, you know,
once you get a taste of this, it's a
little bit like, you know, selling
street drugs. Once somebody gets a taste
of it, uh if it if it's a good
experience for them, they go deeper. And
we are we are having in the last two
years and this is you people need to
really understand what's happening here.
The super wealthy, very sophisticated
players in the last two years have been
studying this market and they're now
coming in and they're coming in with a
very different appetite
for consumption of Bitcoin. They're this
is not the prior 13 years. These are
professionals like I've been buying
Bitcoin as a 20 15 to 20 year play. I am
not getting rid of my Bitcoin. It is a
real estate play for me. I've been doing
this my whole life.
Um, you you want to compare real estate,
the real pain here, compare Bitcoin to
private equity. I've been building
businesses my whole life. I probably
will never build another business, an
operating business because I have found
a holy grail where I have growth over
13, 15% a year with zero human error
risk. Zero human error risk. You just
heard my dogs. My dogs weren't supposed
to be barking. So, I have a human error
risk. Somebody here is not paying
attention,
right? It's a problem though, right? It
is a problem. So, if I can invest in
something that that could go up 12 or
13% a year
and
>> that's pretty conservative.
>> Bitcoin's been doing 45 and 50.
>> A 12% investment per year, you become
wealthy over 20 years. Okay, that's
super returns. I don't know what
everybody we're looking at 45s. I don't
I I look at it and go I'm happy with 13,
dude. I'm all in on Bitcoin.
>> Bitcoin will give me a 13 Bitcoin will
give me a 23% yield over 20 years. Would
you do that? Of course you would. Do the
math on that trade.
23% money is going to be doubling every
three or four years.
>> Every three or four years. $1 million
>> goes to 2 million in three years. 2
million goes to 4 million in year six. 4
million goes to 8 million in year nine.
And and you could take that with a 100
grand. So 100 grand and people are young
people are looking at me going, "Well,
that's not a great return. Like I can't
put a 100 grand in Bitcoin." I'm like,
"Oh my god, you guys are going to end up
broke. You're going to end up broke
because you don't understand energy. You
were talking about young people earlier,
right?
I think they're confused. I I think they
need to understand you're getting ready
to get on a racetrack of life
and it has many turns and swivels and as
as things get more complicated, the
track gets more complicated and no one
has considered how much fuel they need
for the journey.
Somebody would say okay if you look at
the return of big tech stock they do
better than Bitcoin this year. So like
what is this big deal?
>> Well let's let's compare that. So Nvidia
is a 26y old company
>> Bitcoin 16.
If the CEO of Nvidia were to die in an
airplane crash,
his stock most certainly would change.
Now, I love using Nvidia as an example
of the big tech stacks. Uh you do agree
that if if Wong uh got hurt, you know,
the stock price would reflect a
risk. So would Elon. This is why do not
invest with Elon stocks. If Elon dies
one day, come on. Keyman risk. Keyman
risk. Keyman risk. Keyman. Human error
risk. Wow. I have this thing, Bitcoin. I
don't have any of that. Nvidia
is a $4 trillion business.
You cannot possibly tell me where all
their assets are. It's a $4 trillion
business. By the way, we've never had a
$4 trillion business ever. Took 26 years
to get there. Bitcoin 16. It's two
trillion.
Nvidia is a company. It's got paper
contracts. It's assuming the future
income stream. Bitcoin assumes today's
value is 117,800.
It accepts no future value. This is
something that people don't really
appreciate. Bitcoin is literally worth
what it's worth right now today is the
bid just like crude oil. And right now
that marginal unit is 1177.
There is not ever going to be a stock
split on Bitcoin.
There will be stock splits on Nvidia. We
had a quarter of a trillion dollar move
in one6 hour trading cycle on Nvidia
went up and and people are telling me
that Bitcoin cannot move 10 and 15 and
20% in one day. you're absolutely out of
your mind. It is exactly looking at the
tech stacks that you would look at
Bitcoin and go, "Oh my god, this is the
holy grail." This is literally like
finding
a mine in your backyard full of gold and
no one is going to the government isn't
going to seize it. Your neighbor's not
going to shoot you in the face and take
it all. And all you have to do is do
nothing. Sit on it. Hold it and protect
it.
It's it's a finite. I don't think we've
ever had finite.
>> That's the thing. Like people think it
sounds too good to be true.
>> I know.
>> And they're
>> I know. The only thing I can show share
with you is that you are one of one. And
you're not one of 21 million. Bitcoin is
one of 21 million. There's only ever
going to be 21 million. This is how I
really got in interested in Bitcoin.
Quite frankly, it's a bit philosophical.
I realize that you and I
have a really difficult time
as human beings establishing value. We
want to put numbers on things to
establish value. I had a man once tell
me, he said, "You know, I know I know
the price of everything and down to the
penny and the value of nothing." And I'm
like, "Wow, that's that's heavy duty,
man." Okay, because see, the value to me
of living is worth more than 2%. Oh, I
got a cheap interest rate. I'm not going
to move for six. To me, it's like, wow,
I'm not going to live my life that way.
>> When I when I realize that, um, I'm
going to initially as a human being, I'm
going to look at you and go, "Wow,
there's Bonnie. Bonnie. Bonnie's one of
one." And I don't even value her. We
argue with each other. We we Hey, what's
the difference in you? What's the
difference in me? You're Asian. I'm I'm
an Anglo. What? Whatever. Right. We And
I'm like, wow. Human beings have no
capacity to value finite
>> because we argue with each other all the
time instead of looking at you going,
"Wow, look at Bonnie, man. She's doing
unbelievable. She's an incredible one of
one a creature." And then I start
looking at Bitcoin going, "Damn, man.
There's an infinite amount of paper I
can buy on Nvidia.
There is a finite volume of Bitcoin.
It's never going to get accelerated. My
commodity background in energy is very
very important here because I have never
ever not been able to find a barrel of
crude oil or a unit of natural gas or a
kilowatt of electricity. It's simply
about how much am I willing to pay to
get it out of the ground. Is it 60, 70,
80 or 100? We will never see $100 crude
oil again ever. All this stuff about
energy that gonna go up
>> because most 20 a good 20% of the energy
that we
have found we don't even use. It's
behind the pipe. It's just sitting
there. This and Bitcoin's going to suck
it up. It's going to suck it up because
right now that energy is getting zero.
>> Of course, people are going to go, "Oh,
wow. I have some wind there. I have some
thermal. I have a natural gas
uh well over here that's got 20 million
cubic feet a day in it. It's trapped. A
pipeline's a 100 miles away. I'm going
to mine Bitcoin. And every country on
the planet is going to do this because
it's just money sitting there. You're
literally converting wasted energy,
stuck energy, trapped energy, and you're
converting it into a storage unit of
monetary value. And you get to determine
when the timing is. Think about all the
natural gas producers in the world that
store natural gas for three and four
months of the year so that they can have
that natural gas available when they
need peak, right? When when the weather
gets inclement, it costs 30 cents a
month to store a unit of natural gas.
Well, natural gas in America is priced
at $2.50. You're going to spend $3.60
storing natural gas here. Of course,
you're not. Not if you can convert it to
Bitcoin.
You're literally storing gas with a
third party and paying a third party to
store your He's making money on your
storage instead of you just storing it
yourself in Bitcoin.
>> Okay. Why aren't people doing that?
>> Oh, they will do it.
>> The econom the economics will drive them
to do this. It's all now economics. Pe
people will look at this is found money.
This is just found money, right?
>> Okay. I'm wondering, you talked to a lot
of super mega rich people, right? Family
offices, billionaires, uh, of course,
and also people that only has like,
let's say, $5,000 in their pocket. How
would you explain Bitcoin differently to
each type of investors?
>> Uh, first off, I don't hang around that
many billionaires. I find them really
boring. Um I think investing $5,000 I
don't think it's any different. I I I I
don't think um
well I I think the the the real
bad message to the $5,000 player is
this idea on diversity and that you need
to spread your bets around. I I don't
know any successful gamblers that show
up and bet on 10 tables at one time. I
don't know anyone that has 10 wives at
one time, tries to make that work.
Diversity is a total
ridiculous story. Almost like real
estate.
Um,
no, you know, no one that's gotten super
rich unless they inherited the money.
And that is super concentrated, by the
way. There's no diversity in inheriting
money. Zero. You don't even get a choice
in it. Um,
I I don't think anybody actually gets
rich unless they concentrate.
Name name one one person. I mean, Jeff
Bezos
had all his wealth in Amazon.
Anyone that's ever built a business,
almost 90% of their wealth and 90% of
their time is wrapped up in a private
equity company. Something I've only ever
done. 12 years in one deal, eight years
in another deal. I'm broke six years of
my life and then I get overpaid. I make
a ridiculous amount of money and then I
start over.
If I can do that same thing, if I can
invest $5,000 into a franchise
that has 400 million marketers, it has
less than 2%
um integration into a global market. It
would be like, you know what it costs to
own a McDonald's franchise? Two plus
million dollars.
>> Is it a onetime fee or like annual? I
don't
>> No. And then you're going to have fees.
You're going to have royalties. You're
going to have contracts. You're going to
have lawyers. You're going to have NDAs.
You're going to have all this. You're
going to have a physical location where
people can break windows.
>> Yeah.
>> People are going to get sick. There's
going to be food poisoning.
>> I can invest $5,000 into a franchise and
see that grow 20% a year. And by the
way, you don't have to stop investing
the five grand. You can invest another
$500 every month and you will become
exceptionally wealthy. This is how
wealthy people get wealthy, man. They
make concentrated decisions. And they
continue to invest and they continue to
invest and they don't see it. They don't
they don't conflate. Oh, my house
doubled in price, but I didn't sell it,
but my Bitcoin doubled in price and I'm
going to sell it. They don't make goals.
When I put money to work, I decide how
long that money's going to work.
When I find somebody I like to invest
time in, I I think about, hey, how many
I'm going to invest time and energy into
this human being. I'm not going to just,
oh, the first time they're late, okay,
you're out.
First, you know, first time I get a
return, pe people don't really think
about their investment as they do. They
spend more time picking the school and
what they're going to study than how
they think about investing. I am
learning
because of Bitcoin. I'm able to make an
investment in Bitcoin because I look at
it as a as an investment in a operating
business with no operators and no
operating risk and no human error risk.
Literally, it's the same. Look, I build
a business. I spend seven years making
no money.
I never pay myself anything. So, I make
no money. and I'm betting on the come
that I'm gonna oh I'm gonna build a half
a billion dollar business and sell it
seven years I sit there um why don't I
look at Bitcoin the same way I have no
employees I have no HR issues I have no
contracts no NDAs I have no one cheating
on me no one stealing my money no one
suing me for Gary didn't hire me
properly Gary said something Gary wore
pink to the office today and it offended
me I'm going to sue him I mean seriously
This stuff happens, right? I just got
through like four lawsuits because we
built a really cool business and we
irritated Visa, Mastercard,
and uh five years of my life just doing
legal. I have no legal exposure
whatsoever on Bitcoin
and I can just keep stacking it on on my
friend. It's just such a wonderful
experience. And then what am I allowed
to do with my time? Oh, Gary's gonna end
up being a damn artist at the end of his
life. That's pretty freaking cool, man.
>> Yeah.
>> I know 35 year old men and women right
now, their lives are set up through
Bitcoin where they are now studying
philosophy and they're raising their
children within they're the mom and the
dad are actually raising the children.
They're not sending them away to a
prison school eight hours a day and they
have really cool lives. I think you know
I mean what if we have a what if we have
a lifeboat here Bonnie that actually
gets us back to some traditional values
that we've lost. And I think it's those
traditional values that have us in this
weird cycle of degradation over and over
and over. And it's money is a problem.
It's gravity.
>> I think when you talk about being lazy,
we're referring to in Asia. There's this
term that, you know, young people think
they cannot fight. Of course, this is a
minority. I don't want to generalize
young people. But there is a small group
of people. They think they cannot fight
the system. They cannot win. I cannot
afford anything. So, I might as well
just lie down and
survive.
I think if you grew up that way then
then you know maybe you go should go
chat with your parents because I think
your parents let you down
>> really I mean I can't
>> a generational thing because housing is
so expensive right uh they look at their
paycheck I will never be able to afford
a house uh getting married is so
expensive the wife uh ask for this and
that right cannot afford it so what What
can I do?
>> Well, I think people can stop spending
money on things that don't generate um
that don't produce something. I think we
spend our money I think people spend
money on a lot of stupid stuff.
>> First off, if you're going to sit there
and be a victim and say, "Hey, a
I know pe I've had people pick me up in
Los Angeles before. What my favorite
driver in the whole world was a Russian
man. He moved here. He had four kids.
They all did doctorate degrees. He's an
Uber driver. Okay. No, a limo driver.
His own deal. Came from Russia. He loves
this country. He's a My daughters are
all at Stanford and every Don't tell me
you can't do Okay, listen to my accent.
I retired when I was 40 years old from
England
with the energy regulators and the
largest monopoly in the world in energy
with this bloody accent. And I just
worked hard. I worked hard. I didn't
blow my credibility. People ended up
respecting me. I never cheated. I didn't
lie. I didn't steal. And I kept my nose
clean. And I became really good at one
thing. And this is the mistake I think
that that many many people around the
world are making especially well
everyone not just the young people.
They they they have no passion.
Like you're you're a victim because you
haven't found your passion of what you
really want to do. And it's hard to find
your passion. You know that.
>> Um and you can get off track. But this
is life, right? But laying down, don't
tell me you can't be a genius. Look, I
think because of the internet, we're
going to find more artists than we've
ever discovered ever in the prior 500
years, just simply through connection. I
mean, real artists, right? I don't know
where all the musicians are, okay? But
but you you smile, but like, hey, that's
a big gap. Where's all the great music?
Like, I could build eight businesses
right now. I cannot find the right
people. And I don't want to do it. I
don't want to do these businesses. I
want other people to operate them and if
it's going to be a real hassle for me,
I'll just keep buying Bitcoin and that
because that most certainly
will be a better investment. I've got my
daughter did 35 poems on a plane one
afternoon. I'm like my and my ex-wife is
like, "Yeah, she's a little lazy." I'm
like, "Uh, no, she doesn't. She's lazy
when she's doing something you want her
to do, but I don't know anybody that's
ever written 35 points. Clearly, that's
her deal, right? She's like zoned in on
it. Well, that's what she should do.
>> So, I you know, you can't vict being a
victim is going to lead you one place on
your back being a victim and blaming
people for your travesty in life. I
mean, it's just not I don't want to hear
it. I got my own problems, right? And
I'm typically the guy that's the
problem. It it's, you know, if you if
you're a victim, go look in the mirror
and go, why do I like being a victim?
>> Um, I think a lot of times they use that
mentality to justify why they are not
successful, right? And
>> I go back I go back to their parents
because their parents should just slap
them and say, "Hey, you you're just
being a child." Okay. It's just being
immature.
Do you think you can share something
like how you grew up and what part of
your story do you think these people
would be very surprised to learn cuz
people look at you and be be like, "Oh,
of course Gary is successful. Like he is
probably handed the playbook or
whatever, right?"
>> Yeah. No, that that now that would be uh
that would be wrong. I really take my
hat off to my mother. Um my mother
when Grant and I were 20 years old, my
mother looked at us one day and said,
"Hey, you cannot come back to this
house, okay? You go find your own place.
Kicked us out of the house. Don't ever
come back here. You guys are animals." I
I will tell you that was the single most
important day of my entire life. The
moment she pushed me out
uh
at 21 years old, I left my zip code. I
left the state. I left the city. And I
would encourage everyone to leave your
zip code. Leave your girlfriend, your
boyfriend, your buddies, your pals,
and go find out who who you are in the
real world without mommy, without daddy.
Call them every now and then. Check in
with them. Cool. But like at some point,
I had to discover who I was. It was
really cool for me. Grant stayed home. I
went out on my own and I started
learning who I was and I realized how
small of a fish I was in a monster pool
and I and I found the right my right
spot and I didn't
get too egotistical such that I was
going to go bounce around and up up my
game. I stayed at one company for 17
years once I found my platform. This is
the difference in Grant and I. Grant
would never work for anyone. I think
he's probably pretty unemployable.
Um, he is. No, he is. I mean, he'll
probably tell you that. Um, whereas I
went corporate and worked with hundreds
of people. I had 600 people working for
me at one time. Um,
from a 12man startup and I I like that.
I enjoyed working with other people. It
was a very intellectually stimulating. I
learned a lot about the macro global
uh world. I would not have learned that
in a smaller business. So, you know, the
message to me is the message is hey,
find a platform, find a mentor,
a teacher, read books. I've been reading
books since I was 22 years old because I
was so lost. I didn't have a dad and
didn't have any mentors. No uncles
wanted to touch us. I mean we were a
lot.
>> What do you mean by a lot?
>> Well, you've met a lot of people and you
know certain people have a lot of
energy. I mean you just like
>> you know you can feel this.
>> This is why I keep saying hey people
need to look inside themselves. There
are different people like you have
unique energy. I have a very unique
energy that is
>> the the biggest goal is the biggest
challenge is really tapping into it.
and and not being ashamed of it and
just, hey, this is me, man, in all its
glory and dirtiness, right? It's just
messy sometimes.
Um,
I, you know, once I found a platform
though, I don't I don't betray it. I
stick in there and I learn from it. I
expand. I get stronger. And that that I
think people are missing that they're
not they don't have the foundation. I've
spent a lot of time reading books from
Arthur's in the 1800s and 19 early 1900s
about how to how to be successful, how
to make how to think differently,
how to tap into I think everyone's a
genius, man, and they just have failed
to tap into it. And my genius is picking
these markets and and making really like
like once I understand something, it
would be a sin for me not to not to plow
into this thing head like you know
somebody said once they said hey
uh I think Scott Bessant was asked by uh
George Soros who he worked for George uh
George uh Bassant wanted to put on a
trade. He said, "Hey, I'm I'm I'm so
sure about this trade, man." And uh
George said, "So, how much do you want
to deploy?" He said, "I would deploy
100%." And he said, "Well, I thought you
were really serious about the trade. If
you were really serious, you'd leverage
into it."
See, that that's real commitment from
champions like, "Oh, wow. This is it.
I'm going all in, man. I'm plowing into
this trade. In fact, I'm going to plow
into it and leverage it." And the truth
is, that is what people do on houses.
They just don't think about it. They're
leveraging their lives into a house
that's not going to give them that great
return
or they're leveraging it into a school
to sit there for six years and think
about, yeah, but where are you going to
be when you get out? I am going to use a
robot. I am not going to use a doctor.
So, I'd be preparing for that.
I would be preparing for the future.
Looking at the future going, "Hey,
what's it going to be like here?"
>> I think you made it sound so easy.
you're like, "Oh, I just left the house
and I found my passion." But most people
do not have the confidence to just go
out into the world to find their
passion. And I think what you said
reminded me of our conversation with
Anthony Scaramucci. So, I'm going to
quote him. He said, um, when he first
started off, um, when you grow up the
way he did, you're born with this
insecurity. You know, his dad was a
bluecollar worker. He's never been in a
commercial office building. It was very
intimidating. So, he had to learn. And
if he could go back, he would tell
himself to be more confident.
But a lot of people never conquered
that, right? They never worked through
it. I I don't know that anybody unless
you you grow up with a silver spoon and
you grow up in the country clubs
and quite frankly most of those people
they they've never been people I hang
out with anyway. So it's not like
I'm not saying all but it's just not the
world I grew up in. I like I like very I
I don't need somebody wearing a bunch of
fancy watches and driving fancy cars to
impress me. I money does not impress me.
It does. It doesn't. It's how you
behave. Look, I think Anthony and I
probably grew up fairly uh fairly
similar. Uh clearly our politics are
appreciably different, but I've always
felt awkward. I've most certainly not
been a part of the club, and there are
clubs,
double handshakes and the whole deal. Um
I've always been on the outside, so I
actually feel like I'm on the outside of
Scaramucci's club.
But you know the truth is I really have
zero interest in being anybody's club
>> because clubs get weird. I have been
very successful outside the system
beating the system and my expertise has
literally been moving into legacy
markets. By the way, we're punching
right past $118,000 right now in
Bitcoin. You do these interviews and you
get all-time highs. Bonnie, go Bonnie.
Um,
>> yeah, this is a monster move here.
What's happening here in Bitcoin in the
last day, it's a big deal. Uh, by the
way, the more this price goes up, the
more the rich are going to plow into
this thing like you've never seen it
before. This is the second stage of
Bitcoin. This is going to be the most
impactful stage of Bitcoin's history.
I'm going to say that again. more money
is going to be made in the next four
years and kept
than the
>> Can I know why you say that?
>> Why?
>> Why do you say that?
>> One, nobody's losing any Bitcoin today.
Nobody's disrespecting Bitcoin at
$118,000. Three and a half to four
million coins were lost on Bitcoin with
self custody because they did not
respect it because they mispriced it.
Everybody mispriced it. We're still
mispricing Bitcoin.
Act absolutely still mispricing it. Um
at 118,000
the super rich will come in here not
even think about it. They they they
actually want to see this number really
strong.
And the stronger it is, the they're
going to just they will think nothing of
that it was at 34,000 a year ago. They
will not even think about it
>> and they will hold this longer than the
old the prior Bitcoiners.
They will hold it much longer. This is
this is a generational wealth and power
event, an opportunity the lengths I've
never seen before.
>> Is it because of the price? Is it
because of politics?
Is it because of
regulation? Why now? you you know I'm so
glad that Trump didn't get in office in
because Bitcoin wasn't ready.
>> Mhm.
>> It it's really interesting that because
I think he got that probably taken away
from him and I'm cool with it because we
were not ready something like ma almost
magical happened. We needed that period
where we saw the other side go really
draconian.
uh they did everything they could to
stop Bitcoin
and now there's zero regulatory
risk. I mean zero there's zero
regulatory lack of clarity about
Bitcoin. There there's 100% clarity.
They just changed the dealer broker
rules on reporting made it even easier.
There's zero zero headwinds on Bitcoin.
Now we we have people like Ricardo
Selenus. If you haven't interviewed Mr.
Selenus, he's awesome. Okay, you should
really do that. He's one of my favorite
people in the whole world. Um, going to
100% allocation. 76 78 year old
billionaire. 100% allocation. He's
moving off of gold.
>> He's moving off of gold.
Bitcoin's a $2.2 trillion market place.
The gold market just in jewelry
is six trillion.
See, people talk about the whole gold
market. I'm like, hey, why don't we just
take out the the jewelry part of it
first,
right? Or the industrial use of it. So,
we have a long way to go here. This is
just like uh the internet 1995.
>> If you meet a person handling family
office, is this how you would explain to
them? The way I explain it to them is I
ask to look at their the rest of their
portfolio. I simply, hey, can I see your
portfolio? I I don't need to see how
much. I just need to see what you're
invested in. Philip Mars, this Nvidia,
blah blah. Okay. Hey, look right over
here. You got a 2% yield on this thing.
Why wouldn't Would you like to do
better? This is not hard to do. Hey, let
me take your dogs. Let me take your your
crappy investments
and let's can't get any worse than 2%.
Uh I've gone to people before, Bonnie,
that had half a million dollars sitting
in cash and said uh they're making 3% or
4%. Um and said, "Look, I'll guarantee
you 5%.
And I'll give you some of the upside."
>> I went to my sister, she she banks with
Bank of America. I said, "Diane, do you
do you trust me more or less than Bank
of America?" She said, "Well, I trust
you more." I said, "Give me that
$300,000.
I'll give you 100%
I'll give you 1% more than you're making
and 10% of the upside,
right?" Well, I'm going to help my
sister. She doesn't want to take her 300
grand into Bitcoin. So, I'll give her 5%
and I'll put it into Bitcoin and then
I'll give her some of the upside and she
will become very converted into Bitcoin.
That's the way you convert Bitcoiners. I
mean I mean people that are from the
legacy world, hey, let me I'll take it.
I have decent credit. That says a lot to
a rich guy when you go, hey, I'll take
that trade from you. I'll protect you on
that trade. And that there are going to
be products out there like I would offer
someone a six and seven% yield a year to
borrow their money. I would if you guys
want a 6% 7% yield without housing,
without having to lock yourself into a
location, I would most certainly do
that. And there will be institutions
that do it.
So we're we're going mainstream here
now. This is literally uh we are tapping
into the worldwide market and the
addressable market on this is never I
don't think you can actually calculate
the addressable market for Bitcoin
which is really really interesting.
Am I am I too bearish?
>> No. No. Actually, there was this very
interesting moment in our last
interview. You you asked Rent, "What if
we could borrow 80 cents on the dollar
against Bitcoin? What would happen to
Bitcoin price then?"
>> Yes.
>> Let me answer one question. What would
happen to real estate if you couldn't
borrow 80 cents on the dollar?
>> And I want to know your take. What do
you think would happen?
>> Uh I think price of Bitcoin would
probably go up six or sevenx.
If you couldn't borrow 80 cents on the
dollar, in some cases 90 95 cents on the
dollar to buy a house, what would the
house be worth?
And that's the question nobody wants to
answer. That's in real estate. So he
said it would get cut by 30 or 40%. No,
it would get cut by like a lot.
See, I don't think anyone can afford a
house. And I actually think these house
prices going up like this is excellent.
This is the way markets work. You let
the price go up so high that people stop
buying them. Then what happens? They all
rent and then the prices come down. No
one wants to own a big old heavy house
and prices come down. Okay? Or the next
stage will be, oh h I think I can build
some AI technology to build a house for
50 cents on the dollar. And that's
happening right now.
So this inflation thing, like if you're
in a house, I'd be selling the house. I
do not think this is sustainable. You
can't keep going up 8% a year.
It It's not. And the only reason it's
going up is because you can borrow 80
and 90 cents on the dollar.
That's it. Okay. Why do people
that only have $5,000 to invest in
Bitcoin own a $60,000 automobile?
By the way, they don't own it.
>> By the way, they don't own it.
>> They make a hundred grand a year and
they go buy an Audi for 60 grand. That's
going to cost them a hundred
>> cuz it looks cool.
>> Yes, exactly. You should have bought a
1980. In fact, oh, by the way, you only
use that vehicle 4% of the time.
Now, that is a gross misuse of energy
just to look cool. I have one I have one
car, man. You come to my house, you're
not like, "Hey, how many cars do you
have, Gary? Who gives a toss?"
Like, why would I need a bunch of cars?
I only use one of them.
>> There is this saying. So, when you meet
a bunch of, let's not say mega wealthy,
well, rich people, they're always nicer
because they have less problems. But if
you meet, you know, people that are
struggling, they're worried about the
next meal. They're worried about my
hourly pay.
they're not going to be as nice because
they have so much on their mind. So, a
lot of times, you know, I talk about my
guest being amazing and being very
patient and very nice with me. I'll see
comments like, "Of course they're nice.
They are rich. They're not, you know,
worried about the next meal." Things
like that. And I want to know how you
would respond to that.
>> I got to tell you, I've met more poor
nice people than I have rich nice
people.
Um, and and you know, having good
manners on a podcast is totally
different than actually being a really
nice person. So, uh, I've learned much
more from completely broke people. Uh,
by the way, I, you know, I think one of
the great little tricks in life is to
make sure you don't just listen to rich
people, okay? That you actually open
your ears for that. The most impactful
people in my life have been people that
have come into my life for like two
days,
one hour, 12 minutes,
and they left me with a gift. And had I
judged them by the way they looked, I
would never have listened to a word they
said. Had I listened to how much money
they had, uh, I I would have just
dismissed them. So, um, if you want to
find out how flawed you are, make a
shitload of money,
okay? Because these problems do not go
away. I am exactly, it will actually
exasperate my insanities.
Any kind of neurosis I have, it'll get
worse with money. Okay? Any kind of
weirdness I have, you'll be challenged
at every level. Okay? When I was six or
seven years old, I was in a church and I
remember the priest. I can't believe I
This really impacted me that the priest
said I was grew up Catholic. He said it
is easier for a camel to get through the
eye of a needle than it is for a rich
man to get into heaven.
>> When we met in Vegas not long ago, that
was like two months ago, and you and
Grant were super warm. There's this vibe
that you guys are the same on and off
camera. So when you say people want to
present themselves very well because
it's a podcast, I think there's some
truth in it, but also, you know, you
want to look at a person when they're
off camera and I feel like you guys are
super real and honestly it was very
refreshing. We'll have you on hopefully
soon again.
>> Have me on when it hits 140.
>> Won't be too long.
>> That is soon. That is soon. Thank you,
Gary. Thank you. Thank you.